Hello, I'm Ayana, your interviewer, and I'll be talking to you today.
She is Ayaka Yasumoto, the number 5 student in Ebisu Junior High School.
Speaking of Ebisu Chugaku, they went to New Zealand last year.
We often go abroad, too.
But there are so many of us in Ebisu Chugaku.
I think it's like a school trip with 10 members.
Did you have any memorable experiences in New Zealand?
I wonder.
I don't know, but we really went on a school trip as the theme of the show.
We were allowed to go to New Zealand to record a program.
We went to a power spot together.
We had a bit of variety in the recording and on location.
And we ended the show with a live performance.
I think it was the first time for me to spend a lot of time with my younger sisters.
It was probably the first time for me to have such a deep relationship with my sisters.
I was able to get to know the personal side of each of them, and during the recording, Cocona is a pretty funny girl,
I was able to get to know the personal side of each one of them, and I was able to see that Cocona was quite a goofy girl and would say funny things,
It was in New Zealand that everyone's impression of the younger sisters changed drastically.
It was really like a school trip.
I didn't have that image at all.
I had this image of a mermaid who's beautiful and sound-like.
When she's dancing she's so cool, but when she talks she's a bit silly.
They're adorable.
They're all pretty good... even the younger sisters.
There's a lot of fun in her.
I think New Zealand brought out the best in them.
This is very personal.
I love to go abroad. Do you have any good meals in New Zealand?
I don't know why I say "food" because New Zealand is actually New Zealand.
There are not so many specialties of New Zealand.
I have been to New Zealand many times and the first meal I had was Chinese, and the next day I had Vietnamese.
The next day I went there, it was Vietnamese food, and so on.
Yes, Tonkotsu Ramen!
Very Japanese!
Yes, Japanese ramen is very famous.
But it's a very organic country.
So the seasoning is a little bit lighter.
And they are particular about vegetables.
It's a bit like New Zealand in that it's a bit health-conscious.
But the food itself is pretty much the same as in Japan.
The food itself is pretty much the same as in Japan.
Ame Arashi really likes food.
That's right.
I eat a lot of food every time I go abroad.
But there are a lot of people who get hungry.
That's right.
What do you do when that happens?
So we eat a little bit of everything at that time.
Or share one dish with everyone.
When you're on a one-man line, you don't eat much for breakfast or lunch, but share a small portion of a variety of food with everyone.
In a one-man line, you don't eat much for breakfast or lunch.
And then eat a big meal afterwards.
Are you sure you're strong enough?
I'll have a banana.
Bananas are good.
My voice teacher told me to eat bananas.
I can move pretty well after eating bananas.
I see.
I can move a lot when I eat bananas.
I have one more question.
We don't always have seats on the plane.
Flowers and stuff are really loud and they mess with us.
I don't have that image.
There are members who don't want to be next to Hana and members who don't want to be next to me.
and others who don't want to be next to me.
There are various members who don't want to be next to me.
We don't have a fixed seat every time, but sometimes we have a fixed seat.
a We have an attendance number, so we usually line up in order of our attendance number.
So we usually use the order of attendance number, so the seats are usually filled from the front.
On airplanes, for example, the seats are usually filled from the front.
Buses don't really have unassigned seating.
I don't want to give the wrong impression when I say this, but in that long scene in the back...
The seats are still the same from last season, and from there...
Are there any new members who joined the group?
Are they too noisy or rude?
A noisy member?
I wonder who it is.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'm surprised.
I think she talks all the time.
I don't know...
I don't know.
She's a recluse. She never leaves the house.
I think she wants to talk to people.
I think he's just got a lot on his mind.
I see.
When you get together with the members...
You don't sleep. You talk all the time.
I'm fine.
That's great.
You turn your head back and talk to me all the time.
I feel like we talk all the time.
I feel like we have something in common.
I'm a very talkative person.
I'm also a very talkative person.
I'm still talking all the time by myself. I'm a soliloquy type. I'm a soliloquy type.
So you might say that Yuno is a soliloquy type. Surprisingly.
He talks all the time without knowing who he is talking to or about.
Oh, we are the same. They are the same.
I'm often asked who I'm talking to.
I often say that. Yuno-chan is the type of person who says that a lot.
That's the type.
Who do you actually talk to when you're in that situation?
Actually, I talk to myself.
It's okay, you don't have to ask.
I'm totally fine with you talking to yourself.
You don't need me to reply or anything?
No, I don't.
But there are times when you're really talking to me.
There's not much difference between when I'm really talking to you and when I'm talking to myself, so they don't notice.
I've been told by the negatives that I'm ignoring them because I'm talking to them, and they're like, "Oh, really?
I see what you mean... that's a little bit of a problem on my side.
That's what I'm trying to tell her now.
I pay a lot of attention to her.
You're a one-person type.
Yuno's the type that doesn't really need to be listened to all the time.
She's the type that doesn't need anyone to listen to her all the time, so she just talks and talks.
That's all.
The end.
Did you really talk by yourself?
I was talking by myself, and then I just walked backstage.
He came into the dressing room and said, "There's something going on at the end of the room, something like this.
and then he'd just disappear.
He would disappear when no one answered him. It was really interesting.
It's interesting to see something you know.
I'm glad I got to know you a little bit.
I'm glad. I've always loved you.
I've always loved you, Yumichu-san.
I've been doing choreographed copies, diamonds, Oh My Ghosts, at home...
I would imitate Ayaka's power and sing along with her.
I used to sing along with Ayaka-chan's power, and it's something I've always wanted to do.
I'm so happy!
I was so happy to have a lot of conversations with you.
I had a lot of fun, too.
I'm not very good at it.
Thank you for that.
Thank you very much, and lastly, to the Ebitu family who are watching Account Idol, it was a lot of fun. I'm not very good at it. Thank you for that kind of thing already.
Finally, please give a message to all the Ebitu family members who are watching this night and idol.
We are going to release many songs and have many live performances this year, so we hope you will come to see us.
Our album Indig Harbor will be released on the 28th of February.
Please listen to it!
Thank you very much.
And that's it for our special interview with Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku on their 15th anniversary!
Our guest was Ayaka Yasumoto!
Thank you very much.